RG 062:132, Town of South Windsor
Connecticut State Library
Town of South Windsor records
1845-1922
Connecticut State Library
South Windsor (Conn.)
17.5 cubic feet
Administrative, election, school and tax records for the town of South Windsor.
RG062_132
T000972
Historical Note
The town of South Windsor was incorporated in May 1845 and was taken from East Windsor.
Scope and Content
Administrative, election, school and tax records for the town of South Windsor.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Voting registers -- Connecticut -- South Windsor; School enrollment -- Connecticut -- South Windsor -- Statistics; Schools -- Connecticut -- South Windsor -- History -- Sources; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- South Windsor -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- South Windsor -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- South Windsor -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- South Windsor -- Registers
Places:
South Windsor (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1845-1922
  - Treasurers' accounts, 1845-1886, 1893-1908; 2 volumes
  - Treasurers' record of taxes collected, 1908-1914; 7 volumes
  - Collectors' accounts, 1885-1907, 1901-1909; 2 volumes
  - Tax Liens, 1878-1895, 1896-1913; 2 volumes
  - Assessors' records, 1908, 1913; 2 volumes
  - Abatements, 1845-1912; 1 volume
  - Town Deposit Fund accounts, 1845-1905; 1 volume
  - Electors and applicants lists, 1904-1922 (Box Box 1)
  - School Fund accounts, 1857-1877 (Box Box 1)
  - Visitors' records, 1856-1865, 1873-1887 (Box Box 1)
  - Union District meeting minutes, 1900-1913 (Box Box 1)
  - North and First District meeting minutes, 1814-1899 (Box Box 2)
  - Second District records, 1839-1899 (Box Box 3)
  - Middle and Third District records, 1830-1899 (Box Box 3)
  - Fourth District register, 1869 (Box Box 3)
  - Tax abstracts
    Tax abstracts for 1917-1920 are not boxed.
    - Second Society, 1850 (Box Box 4)
    - Second Society, 1851 (Box Box 4)
    - First Society, 1853 (Box Box 4)
    - Second Society, 1853 (Box Box 4)
    - First Society, 1854 (Box Box 4)
    - Second Society, 1854 (Box Box 4)
    - First Society, 1855 (Box Box 4)
    - Second Society, 1855 (Box Box 4)
    - First Society, 1856 (Box Box 4)
    - Second Society, 1856 (Box Box 4)
    - First Society, 1857 (Box Box 4)
    - Second Society, 1857 (Box Box 4)
    - First Society, 1858 (Box Box 4)
    - Second Society, 1858 (Box Box 4)
    - First Society, 1859 (Box Box 4)
    - Second Society, 1859 (Box Box 4)
    - First Society, 1860 (Box Box 5)
    - Second Society, 1860 (Box Box 5)
    - First Society, 1861 (Box Box 5)
    - Second Society, 1861 (Box Box 5)
    - First Society, 1862 (Box Box 5)
    - Second Society, 1862 (Box Box 5)
    - First Society, 1863 (Box Box 5)
    - Second Society, 1863 (Box Box 5)
    - First Society, 1864 (Box Box 5)
    - Second Society, 1864 (Box Box 5)
    - First and Second Society, 1865 (Box Box 6)
    - First Society, 1866 (Box Box 6)
    - Second Society, 1866 (Box Box 6)
    - First Society, 1867 (Box Box 6)
    - First Society, 1868 (Box Box 6)
    - Second Society, 1868 (Box Box 6)
    - First Society, 1869 (Box Box 6)
    - Second Society, 1869 (Box Box 6)
    - First Society, 1870 (Box Box 7)
    - First Society, 1871 (Box Box 7)
    - Wapping, 1871 (Box Box 7)
    - First Society, 1872 (Box Box 7)
    - Wapping, 1872 (Box Box 7)
    - First Society, 1873 (Box Box 7)
    - Wapping, 1873 (Box Box 7)
    - First Society, 1874 (Box Box 7)
    - Wapping, 1874 (Box Box 7)
    - First Society, 1875 (Box Box 8)
    - Wapping, 1875 (Box Box 8)
    - First Society, 1876 (Box Box 8)
    - Wapping, 1876 (Box Box 8)
    - First Society, 1877 (Box Box 8)
    - Wapping, 1877 (Box Box 8)
    - First Society, 1878 (Box Box 8)
    - Second Society, 1878 (Box Box 8)
    - First Society, 1879 (Box Box 8)
    - Second Society, 1879 (Box Box 8)
    - First Society, 1880 (Box Box 9)
    - Second Society, 1880 (Box Box 9)
    - First Society, 1881 (Box Box 9)
    - Second Society, 1881 (Box Box 9)
    - First Society, 1882 (Box Box 9)
    - Second Society, 1882 (Box Box 9)
    - First Society, 1883 (Box Box 9)
    - Second Society, 1883 (Box Box 9)
    - First Society, 1884 (Box Box 10)
    - Second Society, 1884 (Box Box 10)
    - First Society, 1885 (Box Box 10)
    - Second Society, 1885 (Box Box 10)
    - First Society, 1886-1887 (Box Box 10)
    - First Society, 1888 (Box Box 10)
    - 1889-1890 (Box Box 10)
    - 1891, 1892, 1893, 1894, 1895 (Box Box 11)
    - 1896, 1897, 1898, 1899, 1900, 1901, 1902, 1903 (Box Box 12)
    - 1904 (Box Box 13)
    - 1905 (Box Box 13)
    - Union School District, 1905 (Box Box 13)
    - 1906 (Box Box 13)
    - 1907 (Box Box 14)
    - 1908 (Box Box 14)
    - Union School District, 1908 (Box Box 14)
    - Wapping School Society, 1909 (Box Box 14)
    - 1910, 1911, 1912, 1913 (Box Box 15)
    - 1914, 1915, 1916 (Box Box 16)
      On oversize shelving.
    - 1917, 1 volume
    - 1918, 1 volume
    - 1919, 1 volume
    - 1920, 1 volume